### Contact

omololaalimat22@gmail.com

github.com/omolola26

www.linkedin.com/in/omolola2 (LinkedIn)

### Soft Skills

- Problem solving skills'
- Time Management
- Excellent communication skill
- Teamwork and collaboration
- Excellent written and oral communication.
- Strong interpersonal relationship
- Excellent organizational and Prioritization skills

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Frontend Development Training, (2021)
- FreeCodeCamp (Responsive Web Design), 2020

### **PROJECTS**

E-commerce website :( stupefied-shockley-6302ad.netlify.app)

Portfolio : (laughing-curie-5a5a64.netlify.app)

Blog website :( github.com/omolola26/blogfrontend - work in progress)

# **Omolola Lawal**

Frontend Developer: HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | NODE.JS | EXPRESS | MONGOOSE | MYSQL| SQL| REACT | REDUX| BOOTSRTAP |TAWIND.CSS|

Lagos

### Summary

A passionate, self-driven, and result-oriented software developer in pursuit of opportunities in growing organizations that is willing to offer opportunities for career development, facilitate continuous learning, growth, and create a positive impact. Highly energetic and passionate to apply all my skills and professional experiences to achieve organizational goals and also attain a successful.

## Experience

The Bulb Africa - Fellowship Frontend Developer May 2021 - Present (8 months)

### Responsibilities:

- Writing and maintaining code, Learning codebase, and improving my coding skills.
- Frequent design meetings and collaborating on projects.
- Analyze the structure and design of web pages.
- Collaborated with internal teams, including graphic design, web design, and Assembled web pages with basic components using react.
- Debug website issues that arise.
- Track project using GitHub
- Expand database using MySQL and services with Agile/SCRUM methodology.
- Debug website issues that arise.
- · Track project using GitHub
- Expand database using MySQL and services with Agile/SCRUM methodology.

GoMyCode - Fellowship

Jibowu Lagos

Frontend Developer
January 2021 - March 2021 (3 months)

1st floor, Impact Hub Lagos. 7A Milverton Road,	Ikoyi Lagos, Nigeria
Responsibilities	
$\hfill \Box$ Carried out hosting environment, database ad	ministration, and application
scaling which increased productivity by 20%.	
$\hfill \square$ Partnered with backend developers to create	dynamic web pages using
JavaScript.	
☐ Installed and configured software applications	and tested solutions for
effectiveness.	
☐ Wrote reusable unit test documents to ensure	quality control and reduce
bugs in codes by 5%.	
☐ Worked on projects like weather app and recip	be app using Reactjs.
Education	
University of the People - America	
Computer Science · (November 2021)	
ADENIRAN OGUNSANYA COLLEGE OF	EDUCATION - Lagos
Diploma, Linguistics · (May 2012 - 2015)	LDOCATION - Lagos
CORAL BELL COLLEGE	
WASSCE, ART · (June 2010 - July 2010)	
INTEREST	
Listening to Music, Fashion, Networking with pand Travelling.	people

## **REFEREES**

Available on Request